Evgeny Krivosheev



Email: evgeny.krivosheev@unitn.it Skype: krivosheev_evgeniy93 Linkedin: Evgeny Linkedin

Github: www.github.com/Evgeneus

Hello! I am a PhD Candidate at the University of Trento, Italy. My research activity is directed towards optimisation a finite pool classification problem in identifying items that pass a set of filters (e.g., in systematic literature reviews, where candidate documents are screened based on a set of criteria to asses whether they are in scope for the review). To this end, I work on crowdsourcing and hybrid crowd-machine learning algorithms that optimise the screening process with multiple filters, taking into account loss vs money trade-off.

In my projects I mostly use Python language and many py-tools, such as Scikit-learn, Keras, Pandas, NumPy, nltk, gensim, Matplotlib, iPython Notebook, etc.

I continuously learn by reading scientific papers, doing courses, and listening podcasts (Linear Digressions, TWiML&AI, AI in industry).

My strength: Hobbies:

Good communication skills
 Cool team player
 Always seeking for new knowledge
 boxing

Skills TCHNOLOGIES

Crowdsourcing

Python2*, 3*

Machine Learning

Statistics

LANGUAGIES

English (B2, IELTS academic)

Russian (native speaker)

Education

UNIVERSITY OF TRENTO (ITALY)

Nov 2016 - present

PhD Candidate, advisor Fabio Casati

Research topic: cost-aware crowdsourcing and hybrid crowd-machine algorithms for screening items that satisfy a set of predicates.

BELARUSIAN STATE UNIVERSITY (BELARUS)

2011 - 2016

Specialist in Aerospace information systems and Radiophysics

(5 years)

Work Experience

Pi School, Italy

Oct 2017 - Dec 2017

Deep Learning Intern

(2 months)

Won a merit-based 15.000€ grant to attend Pi School of AI, 8 weeks long specialised school with classes and seminars on Machine Learning and Deep Learning, hands-on projects, and mentoring by researchers of the field. I have worked on a cyber-security project focused on Ransomware detection through the analysis of users activity.

Purdue University (USA, IN)

Jan 2016 - May 2016

Internship, research in Crowdsourcing and Data Fusion.

(4 months)

iTechArt Group, Belarus

Feb 2015 - Sep 2015

Junior Python Software Engineer

(6 months)

Responsibilities:

- development endpoints for RESTful Web Services (Python, Django Web framework, Django REST framework)
- design and implementation custom filters and validators (Python, jQuery, HTML, CSS)
- troubleshooting backend problems

Promwad Electronics Design, Belarus

Aug 2014 - Feb 2015

Junior Software Engineer

(6 months)

Design and implementation embedded software utilising the following technologies: C, Bash, Python, Git, GNU/Linux kernel modules, one board Linux computers. micro controllers

Organizational / Managerial Skills

Founder of "Elective of mutual assistance" project at Belarusian State University. The goal of the project is to help undergraduate students to learn mathematical disciplines with assistance of senior students. Me and my team of 10 senior students have been organizing workshops, seminars, lectures. The project has been successfully working since 2012.

Publication

Evgeny Krivosheev, Jorge Ramírez, Marcos Baez, Fabio Casati and Boualem Benatallah. *Leveraging Crowd and AI to Support the Search Phase of Literature Reviews*. AAAI HCOMP 2018, WiP Paper

Jorge Ramirez, Evgeny Krivosheev, Marcos Baez, Boualem Benatallah and Fabio Casati. CrowdRev: *A platform for Crowd-based Screening of Literature Reviews*. ACM Collective Intelligence 2018, Short paper

Evgeny Krivosheev, Bahareh Harandizadeh, Fabio Casati and Boualem Benatallah. *Crowd-Machine Collaboration for Item Screening*. IW3C2 WWW 2018, Poster

Evgeny Krivosheev, Fabio Casati and Boualem Benatallah. *Crowd-based Multi-Predicate Screening of Papers in Literature Reviews*. IW3C2 WWW 2018, Full paper

Evgeny Krivosheev, Valentina Caforio, Boualem Benatallah and Fabio Casati. *Crowdsourcing Paper Screening in Systematic Literature Reviews*. AAAI HCOMP 2017, Full paper

Evgeny Krivosheev, Siarhei Bykau, Sunil Prabhakar. *Detecting and Leveraging Confused Observations in Truth Discovery*. (under revision)

E. O. Krivosheev, I. A. Shalatonin, A. A. Spiridonov, V. A. Saechnikov. *Development of the module for control system, collecting and processing data for the nanosatellite simulator*. VI Belarusian Space Congress, October 28-30, 2014, Minsk (in Russian)